I get contacted by Klei Entertainment and they said,
"Hello aye, we've launched our game Oxygen Not Included,
would you like to make a sponsored video about it?"
I respond, "No, I can't stand video games.
Unless...Unless they have OIL!"
The beautiful black liquid that runs our world
and could make me rich.
They were like, "Sure but, sorry, I don't think-"
"I'LL DO IT!"
Now there's a link on the top of the description if you want to check it out
Today I'm going to drill all the oil this game has to offer.
Then I'm going to print it out and sell it to gas stations
Don't tell me that's not how it works
We won't know unless I try
When you first open the game you need to pick a temperature.
It's up to you, you can pick whatever you want like
terrible fahrenheit
or this disgusting half-breed
or you know, just pure, marvelous, beautiful, Swedish science celsius.
Then, we get to pick an astroid
I pick the first one with Buried Oil
I'm gonna name it "Oil Rig 2"
You aren't allowed to ask me what happened to "Oil Rig 1".
Everyone fails on their first base
This is what you start with
Why would you send humans and not robots?
Because robots cost money and I want to make 100% profit
These are clones...
They are free and have no worker rights.
They are 10 minutes old and know how to dig and follow blueprints.
Only problem is that humans, even clones, need stuff to survive.
Let's find out what they want.
Ugh...these clones were born today. That makes them Gen Z.
So the first thing they want is
electricity
and clean toilets.
When I was a kid,
we dug a hole in the courtyard.
No one died. And the neighbors got some entertainments
Here ya go. Toilets and a hamster-wheel for electricity.
Now you can post your lip-syncing videos kids
while I focus on what you really need...
As you can tell from the game's title,
Oxygen is not viably available on an astroid.
But it does have a lot of Earth's biggest oxygen creators-
algae.
It has all the oxygen one needs.
And that's why doctors say when you are choking,
just eat some of your pocket algae
that all normal people carry around.
We'll put some of it in an oxygen diffuser
and it will spit out delicious oxygen everywhere.
Yet, the biggest problem with humanity is that they become DEAD unless they consume calories.
Don't believe me? Try it yourself
Place one of your friends anywhere and eventually they'll die of starvation.
Farming is one way to grow some food.
But farming requires time, patience, and love.
I have zero of those things
Besides muscles require protein because that what they are ma-
hmmm........
Say...
The average human is 80,000 calories
Maybe we could teleport in some skill-less (?) people
Then you know... CHOP CHOP
Hey guys...
Now I suppose I have to ask for forgiveness
Hey guys, while I build a human-sized oven...
they refused and I can't enforce contracts
when they are on a celestial object.
Fine. You'll be eating algae and lice
Bet you're really regretting ignoring cannibalism now
now that you employees don't starve together,
can we focus on the task at hand?
Drilling oil - making me rich.
Wait. No one knows how to extract oil
My god. We should've just hired professionals.
Ok. I've built research stations and they require more electricity
So I will install the coal power plants.
As you know, always considered that a garbage fossil fuel.
But I'm thinking maybe we can global warm space
and chill out on the astroid surface
There. Research done.
We can now drill oil-
WHAT DO YOU MEAN YOU'RE DYING OF AN EPIDEMIC?!
Fine! We'll start building a hospital
Ok, there you go. I've installed plumbing to help the gas pushers
so we could create refine copper
to solve the electricity problem so that you could have
A JUKEBOX
Now that I have solved literally every problem in human history
we can go DEEPER
It's getting too hot!
TOO BAD! GO NAKED!
Find my oil
We found some. Look at it.
Almost erotic.
Yes, I know it's hot; filled with carbon dioxide
and you have to run through crude oil,
but this is what you signed up-
this is what you were created-
this is what you were destined-
Destined sounds better.
This is what you were destined for.
We have done it. Mission successful
Should I just take the oil now and leave?
No.
What's that old saying?
You gotta spend oil to make oil.
If I replace all our garbage ladders with fantastic plastic ladders
they would be able to climb faster.
Done. But this place can barely keep my ladders repaired
so I gotta search for more.
There's literally no more oil on this astroid
*stammers* at least down here, I can go up right?
YES! I can climb forever.
There is no stopping my thirst for some delicious oil
What am I doing?
What's the point?
I am chasing a delusion
Moving towards madness
I know oil only exists close to the crater
The odds of there being oil to the right of me,
above me,
or the the left of me
are 100% apparently
New idea! Climb to the top of this pool (?) and extract it all
*rumble*
What was that about?
How much oil is back there?
Oh...that's a lot ain't it
Oh no...
Uh oh...
I think this might be one of those "careful what you wish for" moments
Guys, calm down, it's just black water
We need that stuff
Grab a bottle and hold it out
You are really ruining this opportunity
Everyone died.
In the end, 'twas not stress, disease, or hunger that kill the clone.
It was the lack of air
If only, oxygen was included
thank you for watching, click the link on the top of the description to check out Oxygen Is Not Included, i actually liked the game,
but i think i prefer sanbox mode over survival, because i am a causual.
Subtitle credit: kawaii.desu :))), ending credits by Blue